Inventory of the James A. Bill Papers 1940-2003
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Collection of Iran Material, 1975-2004, bulk 1984-2003
  - Crescent International Newsmagazine: June 2000 - January 1992 (13)
    - (13, 23)
      - Volume 25 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1997 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1997 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 16/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1996 (13, 23, 5)
        Subseries 6: Volume 24
      - Volume 24 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 29/1996 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1996 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1996 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 6)
        Subseries 7: Volume 23
      - Volume 23 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1995 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1995 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1995 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 17. 11/18 - 30/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1994 (13, 23, 7)
        Subseries 8: Volume 22
      - Volume 22 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1994 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1994 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1993 (13, 23, 8)
        Subseries 9: Volume 21
      - Volume 21 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1993 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1993 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1993 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No.7. 6/16 - 30/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1992 (13, 23, 9)
        Subseries 10: Volume 20
      - Volume 20 (13, 23, 10)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 10)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 29/1992 (13, 23, 10)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 10)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1992 (13, 23, 10)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1992 (13, 23, 10)
    Subseries 14: Crescent International Newsmagazine Dec. 1991 - Sept. 1982
  - Crescent International Newsmagazine Dec. 1991 - Sept. 1982 (14)
    - (14, 24)
        Subseries 1: Volume 20
      - Volume 20 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1991 (14, 24, 1)
        Subseries 2: Volume 19
      - Volume 19 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1991 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1991 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1991 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1990[excerpt] (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1990 (14, 24, 2)
        Subseries 3: Volume 18
      - Volume 18 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1990 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 22. 1/16 - 31/1990 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 21. 1/1 - 15/1990 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 20. 12/16 - 31/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 19. 12/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 18. 11/16 - 30/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 17. 11/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 16. 10/16 - 31/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 13. 10/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 12. 9/16 - 30/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 11. 8/15 - 31/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 5. 5/15 - 31/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1989 (14, 24, 3)
        Subseries 4: Volume 17
      - Volume 17 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 23. 3/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 22. 2/16 - 28/1989 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 21. 2/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 20. 1/16 - 31/1989 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 19. 1/1 - 15/1989 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 18. 12/16 - 31/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 17. 12/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 16. 11/16 - 30/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 15. 11/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1988 (14, 24, 4)
        Subseries 5: Volume 16
      - Volume 16 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1988 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1988 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1988 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1987 (14, 24, 5)
        Subseries 6: Volume 15
      - Volume 15 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1987 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1987 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1987 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1986 (14, 24, 6)
        Subseries 7: Volume 14
      - Volume 14 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1986 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1986 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1986 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1985 (14, 24, 7)
        Subseries 8: Volume 13
      - Volume 13 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1985 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1985 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1985 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 12. 9/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1984 (14, 24, 8)
        Subseries 9: Volume 12
      - Volume 12 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 29/1984 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1984 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1984 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 13. 9/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 11. 8/16 - 31/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 10. 8/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 9. 7/16 - 31/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 8. 7/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 7. 6/16 - 30/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 6. 6/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 5. 5/16 - 31/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 4. 5/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 3. 4/16 - 30/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 2. 4/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        - No. 1. 3/16 - 31/1983 (14, 24, 9)
        Subseries 10: Volume 11
      - Volume 11 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 24. 3/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 23. 2/16 - 28/1983 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 22. 2/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 21. 1/16 - 31/1983 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 20. 1/1 - 15/1983 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 19. 12/16 - 31/1982 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 18. 12/1 - 15/1982 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 17. 11/16 - 30/1982 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 16. 11/1 - 15/1982 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 15. 10/16 - 31/1982 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 14. 10/1 - 15/1982 (14, 24, 10)
        - No. 13. 9/16 - 30/1982 (14, 24, 10)
        - No.12. 9/1 - 15/1982 (14, 24, 10)
    Subseries 15: Collection of Documents (ASAD) Published By the Iranian Students Who Took Over the U.S. Embassy in Tehran
  - Collection of Documents (ASAD) Published By the Iranian Students Who Took Over the U.S. Embassy in Tehran (15)
    - (15, 25)
        Subseries 1: Documents From The U.S. Espionage Den
      - Documents From The U.S. Espionage Den (15, 25, 1)
        - 47 Volumes: In English and Farsi (15, 25, 1)
  Series 6: Materials and Documents Concerning the Schuman Plan
- Materials and Documents Concerning the Schuman Plan, 1956-1973
  Box 26 contains memorandums, letters, journal articles, newspaper articles, invitations, minutes, agendas and essays concerning the Schuman plan and Bilderberg Group 1956-1973.
    Subseries 1: Schuman Plan Documents
  - Schuman Plan Documents (1)
    - (1, 26)
        Subseries 1: Yale Law Journal Article and Documents concerning the Schuman Plan
      - Yale Law Journal Article and Documents concerning the Schuman Plan (1, 26)
        - (1, 26)
          - Lipson, Leon. Memorandum to George Ball. Paris. 7/31/1952 (1, 26)
          - Bowie, Robert R. Memorandum to George Ball. Harvard Law School: Massachusetts. 2/15/1952: concerning article on Schuman Plan (1, 26)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Memorandum to Robert Bowie. 1/30/1952 (1, 26)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Memorandum to Robert Bowie. 12/29/1952 (1, 26)
          - Excerpt from book: “Chapter 14: The Community’s Responsibility for Preventing Private Interference in the Market.” (1, 26)
          - Draft of “The Schuman Plan Treaty and American Anti - Trust Laws by George Ball and Adam Yarmolinsky. (1, 26)
            With handwritten notes and typed additions to draft: edited
          - Draft: Ball, George and Adam Yarmolinsky. “The Schuman Plan and the Sherman Act.” (1, 26)
          - Abelman, M.A. Memorandum to *Morrie: 1/30/1952 (1, 26)
          - Maril, Mcdoanld*. Memorandum to Adam Yarmolinsky. 12/19/1951 (1, 26)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Memorandum to Joseph Goldstein. 12/17/1951: concerning Schuman Plan article. (1, 26)
          - Goldstein, Joseph. Memorandum to Adam Yarmolinsky. 10/30/1951 (1, 26)
          - Goldstein, Joseph. Memorandum to Adam Yarmolinsky. 10/1/1951 (1, 26)
        - (1, 26, 2)
          - Durkee, William P. Letter to George Ball. 1/3/1951:concerning article (1, 26, 2)
          - Moore, Richard H. Letter to William Willard Wirtz. 2/11/1952: concerning the role of private groups in Schuman Plan. (1, 26, 2)
          - Donovan, William J. Letter to Adam Yarmolinsky. 1/4/1952: thank you letter for article in Revue Parlementaire. (1, 26, 2)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Memorandum to William Donovan. 12/31/1951: concerning article in Revue Parlementaire (1, 26, 2)
          - Memorandum concerning Atlantic Monthly article by General William Donovan. 11/8/1951 (1, 26, 2)
            - Donovan, William J. “The Schuman Plan: A Blow to Monopoly.”1 - 16. (1, 26, 2)
          - Yarmolinsky. “Cleargolaw Washington”: Opinion of Schuman Plan and its European implications. (1, 26, 2)
          - Untitled Draft document concerning the Clarence Randal article “European Steel: Monopoly in the Making,” featured in Atlantic Monthly. (1, 26, 2)
          - Ball, George. Memorandum to Richard Moore? 12/5/1951: Concerning Belgian Publication of William Donovan Article (1, 26, 2)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Memorandum to George Ball. 11/13/1951 (1, 26, 2)
          - Ball, George. Telegram to Adam Yarmolinsky. 11/13/1951 (1, 26, 2)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Memorandum to George Ball. 11/6/1951 (1, 26, 2)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Letter to General William Donovan. 11/5/1951 (1, 26, 2)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Letter to George Ball. 11/5/1951 (1, 26, 2)
          - Ball, George. Telegram to Yarmolinsky. 11/1/1951 (1, 26, 2)
          - Johnson? Letter to George Ball. 10/31/1951 (1, 26, 2)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Letter to George Ball. 10/30/1951 (1, 26, 2)
        Subseries 2: Materials, Memorandum and Letters concerning Schuman Plan Book by George Ball
      - Materials, Memorandum and Letters concerning Schuman Plan Book by George Ball (1, 26, 2)
        - (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Donovan, William J. “The Shuman Plan: A Blow to Monopoly.” From Atlantic Monthly. 2/1952. Pages 58 - 61. (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Donnavan, Gal. “A Propos Du Plan Shuman: Controverse Americaine.” Revue Parlementaire. Libral Opinion: Libre Belgique. 3 - 8. [in French/Spanish, Copy] (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Ball, George. Letter to Clarence B. Randall. 9/29/1951 (1, 26, 2, 3)
            - Randall, Clarence. Letter to George Ball. 9/24/1951: concerning Schuman Plan (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Blondeel, Jean L. “The Schuman Plan: A Peaceful Revolution.” Harvard Law School Forum. 10/22/19523 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Schedule of Belgian Iron and Steel Works. [in French?], 6/1951 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Schedule of Belgian Iron and Steel Works. [in French?], 6/1951 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Schedule of Belgian Iron and Steel Works. [in French?], 6/1951 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Blondeel, Jean L. Memorandum to George Ball. 6/23/1953: Schuman Plan 317 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - “The proposal for an information program for the European coal and steam co Company.” (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Vernon, Raymond. Letter concerning George Ball. 7/4/1953 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Memorandum to Mr. Webster? 5/29/1953 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Ball, George. Letter to Ferdinand Kuhn. 2/24/1953 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Letter from A. Coppe. Letter to Jean L. Blondeel. 2/3/1953[in French] (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Letter to M. Jean. Monnet. 2/2/1953 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Memorandum to George Ball. 1/28/1953: Re. European Coal and Steel Community. (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - “Proposal For An Information Program For The European Coal and Steel Community.” 1/1953 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Memorandum to Jean Blondeel. 1/23/1953: Schuman Plan Book - #3217. (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Letter to Ernest C. Steefel. 1/9/1953 (1, 26, 2, 3)
            - Steefel, Ernest C. Letter to Mr. Lipson. 1/6/1953 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Schuman Plan Purpose. 12/30/1952 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Blondeel, Jean L. Memorandum to George Ball. 12/5/1952: Schuman Plan (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Helmont, J. Van. Letter to George Ball. 10/2/1952 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Letter to Paul A. Freund. 9/23/1952 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Clarence? Letter to George Ball. 8/11/19652 (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Memorandum to George Ball. 7/24/1952. (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Memorandum to George Ball. 7/17/1952. (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - From Ernsteefel. Telegram to “Cleargolaw, Ball etc (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Lipson, Leon. Memorandum to George Ball. 7/17/1952: Shuman Plan Book (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Blondeel, Jean. Memorandum to George Ball. 6/16/1952 (1, 26, 2, 3)
            - “Le Vote Du Plan Schuman.” Libre Belgique. (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Blondeel, Jean L. Memorandum to George Ball. 6/6/1952 (1, 26, 2, 3)
            - Donnavan, Gal. “A Propos Du Plan Schuman: Controverse Americaine.” Librese Opinions: Libre Belgique [French; Copy] (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Yarmolinsky, Adam. Letter to Eric Larrabee. 6/4/1952 (1, 26, 2, 3)
            - Letter to Adam Yarmolinsky from Harper’s Magazine. 5/29/1952: Concerning George Ball’s The Schuman Plan (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Statistical report to Jacques Van Helmont. 5/16/1952 [ 2 Copies] (1, 26, 2, 3)
          - Steefel, Earnest C. Letter to George Ball.5/13/1952: concerning the Schuman Plan (1, 26, 2, 3)